<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Byte Ventures</title>
    <link>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Byte Ventures</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 07:54:32 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Padavan Firmware for Mi 3C Router</title>
      <link>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/mi3c_padavan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 07:54:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/mi3c_padavan/</guid>
      <description>What is Padavan ? Padavan firmware is a custom firmware for wireless routers. It is based on the open-source firmware of Asuswrt, which is the firmware developed by Asus for their routers. Padavan firmware is compatible with a wide range of routers and provides many advanced features, such as support for various VPN protocols, advanced QoS controls, and support for custom scripts and plugins.
It also aims to improve the performance and security of the routers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zerotier - Bypass CG-NAT</title>
      <link>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/zerotier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 06:36:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/zerotier/</guid>
      <description>Zerotier: The Ultimate Solution for Bypassing CG-NAT Are you tired of dealing with the hassle of Carrier-Grade Network Address Translation (CG-NAT)? Look no further than Zerotier!
What is Zerotier? Zerotier is a software-based network overlay that allows you to connect devices, services, and apps seamlessly, regardless of their physical location. With Zerotier, you can bypass the limitations of CG-NAT and enjoy unrestricted access to the internet.
The Benefits of Zerotier Virtual networks that span across different locations: With Zerotier, you can create virtual networks that can span across different locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live an Ad-Free Internet Life</title>
      <link>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/ad_free_life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 07:30:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/ad_free_life/</guid>
      <description>Internet Ads: Now And Then It should come at no surprise to everyone that advertisements on the internet are getting pretty ridiculous these days. They are getting out of hand. You don&amp;rsquo;t just see ads while browsing the internet, through web pages but also in almost every single app that connects to the internet. YouTube, Instagram, Facebook, Reddit to name a few.
Now we get it, Advertisements are the main sources of income for these companies, but that truly doesn&amp;rsquo;t justify the amount of advertisements that are thrown at users these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pi-hole &#43; OpenDNS</title>
      <link>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/pihole_open_dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 19:00:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/pihole_open_dns/</guid>
      <description>What is Pi-hole ? And It&amp;rsquo;s Uses In simple terms, Pi hole is an application that can be installed on linux that acts as a custom DNS server. It can be used to block advertisements and unwanted websites while browsing through the internet. Pi-hole can do a lot more than just this. If needed it can also act as a DHCP server for your network and much more.
How Does It Work ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Huawei B310s-927 &#43; OVPN</title>
      <link>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/huawei_b310s-927/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 20:56:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byteventures.github.io/blogs/huawei_b310s-927/</guid>
      <description>What Does Unlocking Mean ? Here, unlocking means to get access to features that were locked (restricted) by the provider.In this case the provider is the ISP and not the manufacturer (Huawei).
Why Is Unlocking Necessary ? The Huawei B310s-927 is a very famous router provided by ISPs for mobile networks. Meaning, you could use a SIM card to get data and have access to features found in traditional routers. However the ISP modifies the router to only accept their SIM cards and not others&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
